dlgamer.com 2006-06-16

# DLgamer

**7.Privacy Notice :**  
The seller guaranties you, visitors and clients of our website, the confidiantiality of the personal information you provide him. this means :

\- Temporary character of the data collected on the Seller's site  
\- Protection of personal data  
\- Respect of the Franch Computer Privacy Law

The seller guaranties you, visitors and clients of our website, the confidiantiality of the personal information you provide him. :

\- Temporary character of the data collected on the Seller's site :  
In order to fullfill your order, we need to know and memorise some of the parameters that your computer transmits to us : we need to know who you are and what products you are currently buying. Cookies are files used for that sole purpose : memorise, the length of your stay, your identity and the content of your cart as you fullfill it.  
Once you are done shopping, these informations are automatically erased.

Protection of Personal data  
By being a sales site, the seller collects some informations necessary to the handling of orders.

The seller treats all these informations with the upmost confidentiality.

Respect of the French Computer Privacy Law  
According to the French Commercial Privacy Law called "Loi informations et libertés" in date of January 6th of 1978, you have the right to access, rectify, modify et suppress any data concerning you. You can apply this right by writing at the following adress :  
DLgamer  
20, rue des Plantes  
75014 Paris   
France 

or by emailing us at support@dlgamer.com
